Finding aid for the Henry A. Waxman papers LSC.2261
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Personal Office, (1975-2014); (Boxes 233-278)
  - Generic Drugs - Anti-Competitive Behavior, 1998-2000, 2003, 2004 (Box 249)
    RU-486 - Coburn Amendment; Pain Relief Promotion Act of 1999; Global HIV-AIDS; AIDS Drug Assistance Programs; CDC Guidelines for HIV Surveillance 1998; GAO Audit of Ryan White Care Act Programs - 2000; Ryan White Care Act Amendments of 2000; Ryan White Care Act Amendments of 2000 - Title I; Ryan White Care Act Amendments of 2000 - Title II; Reauthorization of the Agency for Health Care Policy and Research; Assisted Suicide; Vaccine Industry Compensation Program of 1999; Prescription Drug Fairness for Seniors Act of 1999; Patent Fairness Act of 1999; FDA Guidance on Pharmacy Benefits Management Companies - 1998; Gene Therapy - 1999; Columbia University and Schering Plough Patent Extension Proposal - 2000; Substance Abuse and Mental Health Services Administration Act of 1999; LA Medicaid Waiver - 2000; Flu Vaccine Shortage - 2000; Human Genome Project; Human Research Subject Protections Act of 2000; FDA Pre-Market Approval and Medical Malpractice; Organ Procurement and Transplant Network Amendments of 1999; Orphan Drug Innovation Act of 2000; Nursing Home Resident Protections Amendments Act of 1999; Dietary Supplement Health and Education Act of 2000; Fetal Tissue - 2000; Medicare Coverage of Injected Drugs for MS - 2003; National Health Care Disparities Report - 2004; Republican Medicaid Block Grant Proposal - 2004.
  - Health Bills, undated (Box 253)
    Mark-Up Materials 100th Congress.
  - Health Bills, undated (Box 254)
    Mark-Up Materials 101st - 103rd Congress.
  - Health Choice Act of 1992, 1992, 1995-1999 (Box 248)
    Morris K. Udall Parkinson's Research, Education, and Assistance Act of 1995; Republican Medicare Cuts 1995; Medicaid - Family Planning and Abortion - 1995; Family Planning; Ryan White Care Act Amendments of 1996; Medical Device Reform Act of 1996; Budget Reconciliation - Medicaid - 1996; Budget Reconciliation - Qualified Medicare Beneficiaries - 1996; Medicaid - Welfare Reform Act of 1996; Health Insurance Reform - 1996; Health Insurance Reform - 1996; Prescription Drug Fairness Act; Drug and Biological Products Reform Act of 1996; Budget Reconciliation - Medicaid - 1997; FDA Reform Act of 1997; Medi-Cal Managed Care Program - GAO Report - 1997; Internet Pharmacy Consumer Protection Act; Drug Demand Reduction Act of 1998; Biomaterials Access Assistance Act of 1998; Better Pharmaceuticals for Children Act of 1998; NIH Office of Auto-Immune Diseases Act of 1998; Ricky Ray Hemophilia Relief Act of 1998; Breast and Cervical Cancer Prevention and Treatment Act of 1999; Republican Medicare Prescription Drug Program - 1999; Medicare Drug Premium Increase - 1999.
  - HIV-AIDS, undated (Box 261)
  - HIV-AIDS-Quarantine, undated (Box 262)
    1980 Mental Health Systems Act; Childhood Immunization.
  - Holocaust Reparations, undated (Box 250)
    Wiesenthal Center Museum of Tolerance; Nazi War Criminals; Aristides de Sousa Mendes; Temple Mount; Jonathan Pollard; UN anti-Israel Bias; Palestinian Authority/Hamas; Hezbollah; Task Force on Anti-Semitism; Soviet Jewry; Syrian Jews; Ethiopian Jews; Soviet Psychiatric Abuse; Soviet Cancer Patients.
  - International Commission on Holocaust Era, undated (Box 252)
    Insurance Claims; Change for Good.
  - Medicaid, 2003-2004 (Box 242)
    Intergovernmental Transfers (IGTs); Under Payment Limit (UPL); Disproportionate Share Hospital (DSH); Dual Eligibles; State Waivers; Medicare 2003- 2004; Prescription Drug Benefit; Medical Privacy Legislation 1999; Legal Immigrant Children's Health; Improvement Act; Pediatric Exclusivity; Hatch-Waxman Background; Women's Health Report 2001; Smallpox Vaccine Compensation and Safety Act of 2003; Drug Discount Cards.
  - Middle East Regional Cooperation Program, undated (Box 251)
  - Patient Bill of Rights, 1998-2001 (Box 241)
    Medical Privacy Legislation.
  - Press Profiles of Rep. Waxman, undated (Box 236)
    Press on "Waxman/Berman Machine"; Op-Ed Pieces Written by Rep. Waxman; Interviews; Miscellaneous Articles.
  - Press Releases, 1975-2014 (Box 259)
    Miscellaneous Campaign Literature
  - Sample Letters, undated (Box 278)
    Thank you letters; Hate mail; Miscellaneous Files: Israel, the Middle East Regional Cooperation Program.
  - Speeches, 1975-2014 (Box 273)
  - Telecommunications, 1976-1986 (Box 263)
    Cable Regulation - 1976-1986; 1980 Cross Ownership Act; Los Angeles County Public Safety Spectrum 1983-1986.
  - Tobacco Legislative, undated (Box 256)
  - Tobacco Press, 1999-2000 (Box 255)
  - Toxic Air Pollutants, undated (Box 268)
  - Toxic Air Pollutants, undated (Box 269)
  - Toxic Air Pollutants, undated (Box 270)
    Chemical Plant Study 1985.
  - Toxic Air Pollutants, undated (Box 271)
  - Trade, undated (Box 257)
    Metrorail; Appropriations/Funding Requests; NBC Reporting on 2000 Presidential Election; Line Item Veto Act Challenge; Proposal to Relocate LA FBI Headquarters to 11000 Wilshire Blvd.
  - Waxman Press Coverage by Topic, 1979, 1981, 2009 (Box 237)
    AIDS; Budget Reconciliation 981; Cartoons; Chairmanship Challenge for Health Subcommittee 1979; Clean Air; De Sousa Mendez - Posthumous Recognition; Energy and Commerce Committee; Environment Family Planning/ Abortion; Fetal Tissue Legislation; Food and Drug Administration; Government Reform; Health Insurance - Catastrophic; Holocaust Reparations Legislation; Holocaust Insurance Claims; Medical Devices; Medicaid Benefits; Medicare Cuts; Mideast Regional Cooperation (MERC); Mideast Iraq; Nursing Home Regulations; Nutrition Labeling; Oregon-Medicaid; Orphan Drugs; Persian Gulf War; Pesticides; Project 28; Tobacco; Vitamins; Waxman Health Subcommittee Challenge 1979; Waxman Whip Race 1989; Waxman Energy and Commerce Committee Challenge 2009.
  - Waxman Video Tapes, undated (Box 243)
  - Waxman Video Tapes, undated (Box 244)
  - Waxman Video Tapes, undated (Box 245)
  - Waxman Video Tapes, undated (Box 246)
  - Waxman Video Tapes, undated (Box 247)
  - West LA VA, undated (Box 238)
  - West LA VA, undated (Box 239)
- Accession LSC-2261-2014-11 backlog material, LSC-2261-2014-11; 8.8 linear feet (2 boxes, 1 half-box, 7 cartons, 2 flat boxes) (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 10, Box 11, Box 12)